: Script and translation
Nazar Ezzeddin
@ NizarEzzeddine
Call me by your name
1983 Summer
The rapist
!he arrived
somewhere in northern Italy
Professor "Perleman"?
Thank you very much for your welcome
My God, you are bigger than you look in your picture
Well, I could not put myself
The whole picture inside, this is a problem
He seems very self-confident
"Lady" Perleman -
"Anilah"
"I am very happy to meet you"
Thank you for your welcome in your home
.you are welcome -
Where is Elio? -
It will be downloaded
"Elio"
No doubt you are tired
!
"Habibi, Come Help" Oliver
In taking his objects to his room
Have you really arrived? -
!Yeah -
.. each one alone of these ..
"Elio", "Oliver"
"Oliver." "Elio"
how are you? -
"I am happy to meet you." I Ilio -
No doubt you are tired
A little, yes -
.Come. Come. Come -
Can I take your things to your room?
.of course, yes -
To my room? -
.follow him
You are more than welcome here
.Yeah
Our home is your home
Are you going?
.Hello -
.nice to meet you
Now clean your room
I'll be in the next room
We would have to share the bathroom
This is my only way out
They are calling us to dinner
..I'm sorry
..Yeah -
They are calling us to dinner -
..Yeah
I will often miss him
Would you apologize to your mother?
Thank you, man
So this is your room, right?
.Thank you
.see you later
I will take care of the cake
Hey! Look at this
Good morning, Professor
.good morning
.. "He rose from the dead" -
Has all this long been grown? -
Sounds like that, right? how are you? -
Well, I'm relieved now, thank you -
Do you like some espresso?
I want some. thank you very much
This looks great. Thank you
Did not I sit in your place?
.no no. There is nothing wrong. I beg you
Have you recovered from your trip? -
.Yes, I did. so far. Thank you -
.OK
Can I show you the place?
It will be great, thank you
Is there a bank in town?
I want to open an account here
Let me do this.
.sorry -
This happens with the best people -
.There is nothing wrong -
No one who lived with us was
He has a local bank account before
Oh really? -
.Yeah -
Do I have to take it to Monto Diy?
I think they were closed for the summer vacation
Try "Grima"
Generous? -
.Thank you -
Is this your garden?
"It's the trees" Anela -
!Thrilling -
.. Peach, cherry, apricot
.. Walerman
"Milograno"
Eat another egg -
Password FAQ Members List Calendar Mark Forums Read -
.no no
, I know myself well
, If I eat the second I will eat the third and the fourth
And after that you will have to turn me back from here
.Tasty -
!my dear -
.thank you
Do I have to give him an "Ankes" bike?
What does one do in this place?
Summer is waiting for it to end
Oh really?
What do you do in the winter?
Are you waiting for summer?
We come here just to spend a holiday
And other holidays
.birthday? I thought you Jews -
And in the Passover also -
We are Jews, but we are also Americans
.. and Italians and French
A rather untypical combination
As well as my family, you are probably Jewish
The only other who landed on this town
, "I'm from a small town in New England
I know what you feel when you are a strange Jew
So, what are you doing here?
Read books
Write a music note
I swim in the river
I go out at night
.I do not know
That sounds fun
.well my friend. thanks for the help
.Sorry
.I am sorry for that
.There is nothing wrong
.Well see you later
What do you have there? -
..This must be -
What is that?
... These .. Follow-up sections of these effects -
.Yeah. Yeah -
. These effects -
.Yeah -
These effects are these residues
It must be historical
Well -
Apricot juice? -
.Yeah
Prefer and drink some -
Thank you.
- Good, dear.
Prefer to drink more
The word "Apricot" comes from Arabic
.. "such as the words" algebra, "" chemistry, "" alcohol
Extracted from the Arabic name is linked
The Arabic definition "A" before it
"The origin of our Italian word" Albicocca
"He" plum
"It is amazing that today in" Israel
, And many Arab countries
The fruit is referred to as a completely different name
.apricot
Can you disagree with me, Professor?
I'll talk to him about derivation
So just give me a second
You are right, in the case of most Latin words
, whose source is found in Greek words
However, in the case of "apricots
It is a slightly more complicated journey
How so?
Well, here is actually Greek
I took the word from Latin
, "And the Latin word is" precocom
, "Or" precookery
Any pre-cooking, and "wild" well-known, of which
"Prekoshas" came prematurely
. "Then the Byzantines borrowed later" Pericos
, "Which became" Pericucci
, "Which later became" Perikuki
"So the Arabs got the" plum
This is a quote from Linguistics 101
May God protect you
He does this every year
, It is time to drink
Let's get in here
"Hello," Romano -
"Hello," Oliver -
how are you? -
.very good -
Hello, boys
how are you? Is everything alright?
.Everything is okay
Can you start, please? -
!Definitely -
.Thank. Thank
Good morning, gentlemen,
.Hello -
How did you find this place?
"Your turn," Oliver -
.OK -
"Come on," Chiara
!Both. Both. Both
.Yeah
He is better than the boy who came last year
Do you remember him?
Push it inside
!Much better
See how handsome he is
"Come on" Oliver -
!Come on! Come on -
!Come on
! Elio ", water"
Well done
!right on time
What is the matter? Are you fine?
Is this a mistake? -
.There is nothing wrong -
.take. Hold on to this
Trust me, I'm getting closer to becoming a doctor
Hey, come here
.do you see? this is the problem
You are strained. You have to relax a bit
I am relaxed
Marsia, "Come here for a minute"
Sindini is here
.look at this
Ateren? He's very nervous, right?
He needs to relax -
"Oliver" -
!See you later
You have to relax more
Well, you guys. are you ready?
Dear, Aunt "Marcella" and others
They are coming for dinner
Will Oliver have dinner with us, or will he come out?
.I do not know
What a movie star
Yes, these are the Americans
Sparkling wine
.it is late
Do not you think?
Do not you think he's rude?
When he says "see you later"?
.arrogant
I do not think he is arrogant
, Just note, this is how he will deposit us
... when the time comes, with his phrase
."!See you later"
At the same time, we will have to embrace it for a while
Six weeks long, is not it dear?
I think he's shy
Enjoy it over time -
What if you hate him over time? -
No, my dear
Take these dishes -
.yes, Ma'am -
..my dear
.. "Elio"
Play something
I do not want to
why do not you want?
.because I dont want to
Why not go to Moscazano with others?
You spoil everyone's fun
!Come on
Play well, darling
.Hello -
What are you doing?
.I read
How can you do, everyone near the river?
I have allergies
.Yes, and I also
Maybe the same sensitivity
What if we and you went to swim?
now? -
Yes, come on. let's go -
Do we have to go right away?
I go to change my clothes -
.OK -
I meet you in the basement
I see you at the bottom
Elio, "What are you doing?"
Read my music
No, you do not
I think, then
Oh really?
What about?
.something special
Why do not you tell me?
.Will not tell you
He will not tell me what he thinks
"Elio"
I think I'm going to talk to your mother
More apricot juice, right?
Thank you, good boy
Thank God you help me
Beautiful
I thought you did not like her
Play it again, okay?
.Follow me
These look different
Did you change it?
I changed a little
Why?
.. I just played just like "was not" will play
"If not in copy" Bach
He plays again
Play what again? -
The thing that I played abroad -
Do you want me to play what I played abroad?
.please
I can not believe you changed her again
I changed it a bit
Yeah! Why?
She has just played the way he plays
"Bozoni" if changed in the version "not"
What would be Bach's problem if he played Bach? -
Bach did not compose this guitar -
.. In fact I am not sure that "Bach" would have written -
! Forget that I have asked -
He is the young Bach
I gave it to his brother
I was very cruel when I said
"I think he hates" Bach
I thought he did not love me
Welcome, Professor
.Hello
Here, please
.Joined
What do you think of this? -
... I think your thoughts here are convincing, but -
!Hello -
Hello -
Have you gone to the river? -
.Yeah -
! "Mavalda"
Pretty, right?
Elio "?"
Are you sleeping?
!I was
Hear this nonsense
Tell me what you think
.wait
What?
.I can not hear you
"For the ancient Greeks," Heidegger says,
Internal concealment establishes a means
, To form what beings
Not only in relation to them themselves, but rather
As well as other entities in general
In other words, understand not only explain the concealment on
"It basically concerns entity relations with humans
Does this have any meaning to you?
That does not make sense to me
I do not think it would be meaningful to APEC either
Maybe it made sense when I wrote it
This is probably the most nice thing
Someone told me a few months ago
.Nice
.Yeah. Nice
.Come here
What is going on?
Is he trying to seduce her?
Elio, "Have you ever done that before?"
How do I know?
I would like to be in his place
Who would not want to be in place?
She wants it whatever it costs
are you coming?
I'll go later
Are you annoyed that you are upset by "Chiara"?
Why should I be upset by Kiara?
.because of him
Because of who?
"Oliver"
Turn on
Will you meet me here tomorrow night?
!Wait for me
.come on quickly
We had sex last night
"Me and Marcia
Why did not you do it?
.I do not know
Well, try better than that, do not you?
All I needed was courage
Access and touch
She would have agreed
Well, try again later
Try .. What later?
I have just heard of people in
Sirmione "They found something"
!Fabulous
I go there today
Do you want to come?
.I'd like it. Thank you
Can I go too?
Under one condition to remain silent
Silent Kun has a lot of opinions?
Or just silent in not telling anyone what it is
The wonderful things you dug into?
, No drilling is done to anything
It is what has been brought to the surface
.from water
What are you doing?
I go to Lake Garda with my father
"He wants to see" Oliver
The place where they are swept away
Can you tell him that I have passed?
It is inside with my father
Help him
. I was amazing last night, on the dance platform
He is dancing well -
.Drive well -
It is also handsome
Do you want us to meet? -
.Both -
Hey, enter
It will be a pleasure to meet today
Only if you promise to wait for me
We will return
My father always sits in front
With Anges to guide
She seems to have loved you, Sahij?
It looks more beautiful than last year
She saw her naked during a night swim
A great body
Are you trying to make me love her?
What harm in it?
Well, there is no harm
I just want to pay attention to these things
Yourself, if you do not mind
I will lead today
Just do not represent the role of a good host
.very good
Thanks Angie, you can leave this evening
What is it, boys?
.Oliver, "Come"
Sit in the front, take turns
What? What?
, Then another thousand...
He added five points
Well, the disagreement is if what
.. "was the name of a poem for" Ctulos
It is for the man himself
"Dr." Rosa!
!welcome
Look here
You know that, right?
"That 's Oliver
!Hello
"Hello" Teresa
"Come here!"
.Yeah -
truce?
Children!
The ship sank in 1827 in
, "Its way to the island" Garda
Rumor has it that this statue was
Gift of Count "Liki" to his sweetheart,
"Contalto Adelaide Malanotti"
There were four known groups yet
. Original sculptures
This is the third
"Had Emperor Hadrian
. "Two, found in" Tivoli
But one of the most popes
, A bourgeoisie of "Parma" has corrupted them
"They were reshaped in a very exciting way for Venus
Who would like to go swimming before we go back?
It is very scandalous
All statues are often of this type
"Elio"
"Oliver"
- Hey!
!Ali! I'm going -
Oh, heaven!
Are you going too? -
..Both. I have to stay and work a little in my book -
Your Lord! What about some drink to celebrate the day?
Well, I might drink a little -
!OK -
Marcia "?"
"Cosmic Fragments"
"For" Heraclitus
, Meaning river flow is not that all things change "
So we do not find it twice, however
Some things remain the same
"Only through change
.Yeah
"Excuse me," Elio.
I brought some clean clothes
Open the door
Thank you.
.you are welcome -
Honey, did you see my "Heptamiron" book?
It is in German
I do not remember where we stopped
But I think you will love this.
Come here, darling
If so, I will translate
.. Farris is a young man fond of love princess "
He is also fond of him
Although she does not seem to be fully aware of it
... and against friendship
.. "Freundshavt"
... which flourish between them, or
Perhaps because of this strong friendship
The young knight finds himself
.. very much and unable to speak
Because he is totally incapable of addressing his love
: Until one day the princess asked frankly
Is it better to speak or die?
I will never have the courage to ask such a question
I doubt that
..Listen
.. إيلي "الجميل"
You know you can always talk to us
My mother was reading a novel
French from the sixteenth century
I have read a few of them for my parents
When the lights were off
Is it about the knight who does not know
Whether he will speak or die?
.Right
So, did he or did not he?
She said it would be better to speak
But she remained cautious
I felt a smell somewhere
So, will he speak?
.Both
Evades.
I thought so
It is French
I have to go to town
A little for some things
I can go
I have nothing to do today
Why do not we go together?
now? -
.Yeah -
.now
Unless, of course, you have more important things
Can I put these in your bag?
.Yes please
The wheels are fitted and the tires are blown
.Fabulous. Thank you
I fell when I was home
, Yesterday I scratched myself badly
Ankes insisted on treating him
A variety of magic recipes
I think he has benefited
Will you hold a moment for me?
Do you want one? -
.Certainly -
Not bad, right?
It's not bad at all
I thought you did not smoke
.I dont do
It's World War II, right?
It is the First World War
You have to be eighty
At least to know which one
"I have never heard of the Battle of Piave
The Battle of Piave was one of the most
The battles were deadly during the First World War
Killing 170,000 people
Is there anything you do not know?
"I do not know anything," Oliver said
You seem to know more than anyone else here
If only you know my ignorance
Things that matter
What are the things that matter?
You know what things are
Why are you telling me this?
Because I thought you should know
Because you thought I should know?
Because I wanted you to know?
Because I want you to know
Because there is no one else I can
To tell him this only you
Do you say what I think you are saying?
.do not go anywhere
Stay here
You know I will not go anywhere
They have mixed all my papers
I will have to rewrite everything
I will not be able to work this afternoon
This will delay me a whole day
.Curse
.What should I say something -
Just pretend you never did -
Well, does that mean we can
Are we talking about these things or not really?
That means we can not
We talk about these kinds of things
OK?
We can not
Hey!
Come on, American
ready? -
.let's go -
are you thirsty? -
.Yeah -
.Good morning, Madam -
Good Morning -
.sorry
Can I ask for a glass of water?
"Ducci"
The people of Italy
.do not go far
.Thank you -
.Pardons -
!Come
These are my spots
All to me
.. I'm here to read
I can not know how many books I have read here
Oh God, the water is frozen
Spring in the mountains
European Alps
The water flows directly from there
I like the way things say
I do not know why you are humiliating yourself
If you do not, I think
Are you so afraid of what I'm thinking?
You make things very difficult for me
"I love this," Oliver
What?
.everything
Do you mean us?
It's not bad
Has it improved now?
No, no, no
.We have to go
Why?
I know myself, okay?
We act properly
We do not do anything shy
This is a good thing
I want to be good
OK?
Do I insult you?
Do not just do it
I think he started getting inflamed
Are we passing the pharmacy on our way back?
.excellent idea
"So we got the government of Bettino Craxi
Because we do not do anything but
Speech, speech and speech
Let me talk
We have five parties that do nothing but fight
Drink and be dumb
Let them talk. he and she
I would like to know what they think too
"What do you think?"
A five - party government
Azizi, I think this is a historic compromise
.Do not say this
The term "settlement" is tragic
, I have changed since I inherited this place
.... Anilla, "You"
What does this thing have to do with that?
What are you saying?
You are crazy, my love
You are very funny
It 's right, you' re a fan.
And you do not tell her anything -
.say something
You quit
Why do not we talk about the death of "Bonwell"?
Bonoil "was a genius"
Do you know him? -
Cinema is not the solution -
, Cinema is a mirror of reality
It is a filter
"The specter of freedom has been introduced
..Although continuous boycott
Everyone loves Bonwell
Let's hear his opinion
He does not know anything about Italy
.say something
Your opinion
Do you have an opinion?
He is American, my love. he is American
American, but that does not mean he is stupid
My love, he 's an American
Just stop
I do not give an atom of corn
Attention to some politicians
She did not say that
You lead me to madness
Lead me to madness
What speeches?
What is the matter?
what is happening?
.nothing
This always happens
Mavalda, "Where is the ice?" -
It's in the fridge -
He gets used to everything completely
Do not you realize that you are everything?
What are you talking about?
No more politics and nothing -
He also left -
Elio "?"
Are you fine?
Sit for a moment
If you insist
That was not my fault, right? -
.Both -
I'm in a mess
Well, the kitchen table is definitely as well
Ah, where did you learn to do it?
My dad used to do this to me when I was sick
Trust me, this helps
I had one like this -
Oh really? -
.Yeah -
Have you ever worn it? -
My mother says we are conservative Jews
.OK
I think this is true for your mother -
- Funny funny -
She will kill me if she does.
I do not hope this -
Hello, are you leaving?
Where is Elio?
It's inside. His nose was bleeding
At lunch now he is resting
Oh really? -
.Yeah -
Well, I'll be back in a minute -
!Bye -
.do not go anywhere
Are you fine?
Will we get out?
I do not know if I can go out
If my mother sees this, she will be worried
Oh really? -
Yes, it's annoying -
Where is Oliver?
Do not ask me
Did not he come out? -
Do not you want fresh juice? -
"No, thank you," Mavalda
We'll have dinner soon
.There is nothing wrong
I'm going out tonight
Do not make me worry -
What are you talking about? -
This is not a good thing, madam
.Day cares about the same things -
.OK -
Why do you reprove me?
I am 17 years old
She is worried about you
You love him, do not you? "Oliver"?
"Everyone loves" Oliver
I think he loves you too
More than you do
Is this your impression?
No, it's the one who told me -
When did he say this? -
.Since the period
Mavalda, "do you know where Oliver is?"
.I do not have any idea
.traitor
"This is" Craxi
"The center of Craxi was painted
.Hello -
Hello -
Yes im this person. Is this "Marcia"?
of course me! Can not you recognize me?
.I apologise
This for me?
Thank you
Do you really read a lot?
I also love reading
But I do not tell anyone
Why do not you tell anyone?
.I do not know
...I think that
... people who read
Tom Thompson
Who are they?
Are you hiding from what you really are?
No, not with you
not with me?
Well, maybe a little
and how's that?
You know exactly what I mean
Why you say that?
Why?
..because I
...Think
You will make me suffer
I do not want to suffer
You have a severe erection
.wait wait
.He kissed me
Is this good? -
.Yeah -
Do you lie?
Damn, I'm sorry -
.There is nothing wrong. There is nothing wrong -
are you mad at me?
What is so funny?
Why are you laughing?
.leave me alone
Damn, it's a good feeling
Please do not avoid me. This kills me.
I can not bear to think that you hate me
.Your silence kills me
I'd rather die knowing you hate me
I am very cowardly
This is exaggerated
I can not keep silent
I need to talk to you
Did anyone spend a good night last night?
.not really
You should be tired
Or are you playing poker, too? -
I do not play poker -
Several hundreds of colored slides for
"Brakstillis" and the others arrived yesterday from Berlin "
We should start by cataloging them
This will keep us busy until lunch, as I imagine
Definitely.
Pretty, right?
All of them are incredibly sensual
Because they are more Hellenistic than that
It dates back to the 5th century
"It is most likely carved by the effect of" Braxetiles
... "
The greatest sculptor in antiquity
.grow up
I'll see you at midnight
The muscles are solid
Look at the stomach, for example
There is no straight body in these statues
It is carved
, Sometimes impossibly curved
It is very uneven
To indicate its ambiguous ambiguity
As if she challenged you to want her
"Do not forget to" Isaac "and" Munir
They will come for dinner
They are also known as Sony and Cher
.OK
I would like you to wear your shirt
We will give it to you for your birthday
.Both
.I'm sorry -
.. "Dear, I have brought it from" Miami -
.It is a very large -
Welcome!
- I'll look ridiculous -
This will make them very happy -
, "I will measure it in front of" Oliver
If Oliver thought I was
I will not wear it like a forklift
Oliver? "
what time is it? -
It is the second -
.Well see you later -
.see you later -
! "Mavalda"
I will not be here for dinner
"Well, Master" Oliver
.Hello -
"Happy day," Mavalda
"Marcia"
where are you going?
.stren
Thank you
!Enough
!Damn
How are you my friend? -
!Hello -
It took a long time -
- Long time, yes.
how are you? -
.I have grown up -
how are you?
See your vision
Do you remember Marsia last year?
.good day
Marcia, "do you remember Isaac?"
The girl from Paris? -
.Nice to meet you -
Listen, do not you want to eat with us today?
.no no. I have to go
are you sure? -
.Yes Yes -
.OK -
Have a happy evening -
Thank you.
.Bye -
.Bye
..that is here
Of the new Chinese class which is
You guys liked to send it to us.
It looks great
"Come here" Mounir
.Come. Come. Come
I can not wear him now. He has met me before
You can -
I will look like the clowns -
!My Father. My Father. I will look like a hawk
Do not do bad things tonight
No laughter
When I tell you to play, you will play
I was old enough not to
Accepting people for what they are
What is their problem?
Sony and Cher call them behind their backs
This is what my mother calls him -
I have accepted this gift from them -
Those who will reflect on it badly are you
Is this because they are lesbian sex
Or because they are ridiculous?
If you know a lot of economics
, As much as "Munir" and he is like your age
You will be a very wise man indeed
... and .. and
And it is my secret
Now, wear this
Sorry, I have to go to bed
Sorry, I'm very tired
Thank you
"Elio"
Thank you.
.Good night -
.Good night
do I know you?
Thank you again for everything
They will never be able to drive -
No, they will be fine -
I'm glad you came
.I am stressed
I loved what I did in the place
Thank you
No, thank you
Are you fine?
.I'm fine
Can I kiss you? -
.Yes please -
What do you do?
.nothing
Does this make you happy?
Your nose will not bleed on me, will it? -
...I wo n't -
!Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out
Drag it only
"Oliver"
Give me your name, and I will call you by my name
"Elio"
"Oliver"
Have we caused a noise?
Nothing to worry about
.Mvalda "always looking for signs"
You will not find any of them now
I was wearing this shirt on your first day here
Will you give it to me when you go?
Let's go swimming
Will you carry what happened last night against me?
.Both
"Elio"
!Come here
!take off your Pants
This is something promising
I got an erection again
!good
Professor, I have received your observation
Thank you for reminding me
I may go to town to bring those
, Printed paper today
So you could have this
Evening is a good time to ..?
.see you later
We'll take a look at you later, before you leave
.OK
..if
!See you later
!see you later
"Oliver"
Have you not bothered me yet?
No, I just wanted to be with you
.. I .. I will
.Go
Do you know how happy I am that we have slept together?
.I do not know
Of course, you do not know
I do not want you to regret anything
I hate the idea that I might have spoiled you
I do not want any of us to pay for it -
- No, I -
It's not like I'll tell anyone
There will be no trouble
That's not what I'm talking about
Are you glad you came here?
I would have accepted you if I could
Time has changed
Thankfully, we had a resistance movement
I know, but time has changed
It is different now
What do you think of "Bettino"?
.I do not like him -
.I love him -
I'm happy, really
I do not know, we will see
In any case, they set the rules
"Pasquina"
.good day
Happy day, madam
Tortelli Kremsky? " -
!Yeah -
!Damn
What have you done?
!nothing
I understood
I have already moved to the kingdom of plants
And then what? the canyons?
I suppose you have already given up animals
You know I'm one of them
I'm sick, right?
I wish everyone were sick like you
Arjok, do not do that
Do you want to see something satisfactory? -
Arjok, do not do that -
.please do not do this -
Hey! please do not do this
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you do? -
...Just -
.you are hurting me
So, do not fight
.I'm sorry
.There is nothing wrong
I wish you would not go
God, we have wasted a lot of days
Why did not you give me a signal?
!I did -
You did not give me a signal -
when did you? when? -
, You remember when you play volleyball
And then touched you?
Just to show you that I loved you
.When I reacted as if I disturbed you -
.I'm sorry -
.Excuse me -
.There is nothing wrong -
When I decided to just keep a distance between us
.I do not know
I come here for almost hours every night
I knew that
This is funny, I have
... I thought it
Yes, I know what I thought -
!Enough! Enough -
"To Oliver, from Elio
"Elio"
I disappeared for three days
I had to work
You have completely disappeared
..Yes, I do not know
...just me
I had a lot to do
Are not you girl?
On "Oliver" to go to
Bergamo "for a few days"
Research at the University
"Then he will leave by plane to his home from Linate Airport
What about Elio?
Maybe it would be nice for the two
To get away for a few days, right?
What do you think?
You know that you are our favorite student
- Go back.
Are you sure you mean it? -
"Oliver" -
Thank you very much, Professor.
!Hey man
!please please. Come back soon
.Count? I'm just coming home to pack my stuff
I will move here
.you are welcome
..OK
Thank you very much.
.Of course -
"Oliver." "Oliver"
!Count
That was great
.Come here. Come here
.You are gorgeous
Thank you guys
..OK
"See you later, Perleman's family
.see you later
.see you later. See you later
!Bye -
.Bye -
Ask Elio to call
When you get there
!Both
Come eat dinner tonight
OK?
"Bring it with you" Marcia
.Bye baby
What? -
.nothing -
"Oliver"
"Elio"
!Yeah
!Gosh
.do it
!Damn
Do you hear that?
.wait. wait
.Both. Both
It is from this direction, come
You'll miss
!Come
Boys, do not stop
This... this... you... you.
You allowed me
One second, please
!One second
I saw this last year
! Richard Butler "... awesome"
Oh really?
We saw them at a concert too
We were on a trip to London
what did she say?
!sorry
Is your passport with you?
Mavalda? "
Hello mother?
.Yes im this person
.Yes, everything is alright
I'm at the station
"In" Clusone
Listen, Mom, can you?
Can you come and take me, Mom?
!Hello
how are you?
.Fine
I read the book you bought me
..pictures
It is really very beautiful
"I loved those..." Antonia Buzi
.. I am sorry, I apologize
.. Because you are very sad
I say that because I wanted to tell you
I am not angry with you
.never
"I love you," Elio
Are we still friends?
forever?
.forever
I missed dinner
and then?
.welcome back
.Thank you
Did Oliver enjoy the trip? -
Yes, I think he did -
It was a nice friendship between you
.Yeah
.. You are very intelligent to not know how rare it is
What a special thing, what you have been through
"Oliver" was "Oliver"
Because that was it
Because that was me
... Maybe that "Oliver" is very clever, but -
.no no. It's more than intelligent -
.. What was between you
It has all the connection and has no connection to intelligence
.it was good
... and both of you are lucky to find the other, because
Because you are also good
I think he was better than me
I am sure he will say the same thing about you
Will he say the same thing?
This is a compliment to both of you
At least I have intuition
Nature has its cunning methods
To identify our weaknesses
...Just
Remember that I am here
At the moment, maybe not
You want to feel anything
Maybe you never want to feel anything
..And
Maybe not with me I want
Talk about these things
..But
Feel, something you obviously have experienced
Listen, you had a beautiful friendship
Maybe more than just a friendship
I envy you
In my place, most parents will hope
The whole thing disappears
.. and pray for their children to stand on their feet, but
I am not the kind of father
We are so hard on ourselves that
We heal faster
Then we get to bankruptcy at the age of thirty
What we have to offer will be less
Every time we start with a new person
.. But to force yourself to feel nothing
.. or that you do not feel anything
!What a lose
Have you talked too much?
I will say one more thing
.. This will settle the atmosphere
Maybe I 've come close to it
But I never got what you got
There is always something
He stopped me
Or just stop in my way
How to live your life is something for you
..Just
..remember
Our hearts and bodies were given to us only once
..And
Before you know it, your heart is eroding
..As for your body
A time will come when no one will look at me
So let him approach him
..At present
There is sadness
.. and pain
Do not kill him
He had the joy I felt
Do you know Mom?
I do not think she knows
Did you go to "Gavirin"? -
.Yeah -
Pies
Can i? -
Happy Hanukkah holiday -
.You too
The girl is highly recommended by
"One of my colleagues at Stafford
..The private area in the study is
I will reply!
Hello?
Elio "?"
are you there?
.Hello
how are you?
I'm fine, I'm fine
How is your parents doing? -
.I am fine, the two are fine -
.good
.I missed you
.I missed you too
.Much
I have some news
News?
Will you marry?
..as I guess
Maybe I'll get married next spring, yes
You did not say anything
We have been separated from two years ago
This is great news
Do you mind?
"Oliver" -
!Hello! Hello
Dear, when will you return?
I wish I would
You are connected and we are selecting the new guest
Next summer
And imagine what? It's a girl -
... cute. Well -
Talking about the news, I am
I call to tell you that I have been engaged
!Fabulous
Congratulations!
!"Good luck" -
"Congratulations," Oliver
Thank you -
..Assum, we will leave you
"We'll let you talk to Elio
Happy Hanukkah holiday -
.good bye dear
They know about us
I imagined this
How?
From the way your father talked to me
Make me feel like part of the family
Almost like a smelter
.You are very lucky
My father would send me to reform
Elio "?"
.. "Elio". "Elio". "Elio". "Elio"
"Oliver"
I remember everything
Call me by your name
: Translate and Sketch
Nazar Ezzeddin
@ NizarEzzeddine
Elio "?"